= kissasia.co =
[Connecting to You]
["Night School Boys" is out.]
[Wanna watch it together?]
[Are you cooking dinner?]
Why are you back, Senior?
Weren't you going to buy lunch?
Did you have a fight with Jiakai?
I was too lazy to go out,
so I asked Lai to buy it for me.
So, was the fight about cleaning
or washing dishes?
How could we fight
over such trivial things?
No.
We don't live together,
so how could we fight over those things?
Don't be so nervous.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
But I noticed you guys
haven't been talking much lately.
What's it about?
[Keke]
Keke.
Why does she have your number?
What does she want from you?
We just agreed to watch a movie together.
Which one and where?
Are you interrogating me
like a suspect now?
You're the one not to tell the truth.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's my private business.
Just...
nothing.
[The 8th Thread]
[Reaction Formation]
[His Prickly Attitude Isn't Intentional]
It's been so long.
Is Professor Zeng really coming today?
I confirmed with the department office.
Professor Zeng will be in the lab
between 3:00 and 6:00 p.m.
[The Department Student Association
Welcomes You]
I don't know why he isn't here yet.
But we've been waiting for over an hour.
Maybe we should just forget it.
I think I'll make an appointment
with Professor Zeng next time
and come back then.
Okay.
Do you have classes this afternoon?
No classes this afternoon.
Great. I'll take you somewhere.
Where?
Just follow me, and you'll see. Hurry up.
Right here?
Welcome to the Old House Bookstore.
The layout here is so unique.
It looks a bit like
my grandparents' old house.
That's right.
This used to be my grandpa's house.
After my grandpa passed away
a few years ago,
my dad considered selling it.
But
my sister and I couldn't bear
to part with it,
so we begged him
to let us turn it into a bookstore.
My sister is in charge of
the behind-the-scenes planning,
and I'm in charge of
the frontline operations.
How long did it take you
to transform it into what it is now?
A long time.
Because we insisted on
drawing the blueprints ourselves,
the design alone took a lot of time.
After the design was finished,
we had to find contractors
to do the renovation
and make all the bookshelves,
tables, and chairs.
Of course, we also kept a lot of
things left by my grandpa.
Why was I peeking? That's her privacy.
What are you doing?
My hands were itchy.
Just a pat, and it'll be fine.
You're back.
What took you so long?
Weren't you going to cook ramen?
Because you didn't reply to my messages,
I ate before coming back.
Are you full?
Of course, I'm full.
How could I wait for you?
Then I'll cook ramen next time.
Why is there a bagpack here?
I don't know.
How long have you
been using that backpack?
Three years.
It can still last a bit longer.
Is it for me?
Good that it's not.
Because I also bought one today.
You bought a new one too?
Yeah.
Did you buy it yourself?
With Chaonan?
Keke?
Anyway, it's not for you.
Don't ask so much.
Good night.
Really? No way.
Wait, I see my friend.
You go first. I'll come over later.
Why are you playing
a two-player game alone?
So lonely.
Mind your own business.
What are you doing here?
Just playing.
Oh my god.
Except for my grandma,
I've never seen anyone play Taiko Master
so badly.
Let me show you who the real
Taiko Master is.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
As a Taiko Master, I'll never
hide anything.
Come on, go ahead.
I just wanted to ask you that
Jiakai said the threads tied to you
were once severely tangled.
That means a bunch of threads
were tied to you, right?
I thought you didn't believe it at first.
Right.
According to Jiakai,
there were indeed many threads.
Did Jiakai ever say
how many threads were tied to him?
Why do you ask?
I was just thinking,
since every time he helps someone,
a thread is created between them,
he should also be someone
with a bunch of threads.
If that were the case, it would be great.
What do you mean?
He was born without threads,
a natural outcast.
However,
except for the one tied to you.
[Chaonan] [Do you want steak?]
[Chaonan] [Or an all-you-can-eat buffet?]
[Chaonan] [Every day?]
Why is he acting crazy
even with a hangover now?
[My treat.]
[Are you full?]
We just came over to see
if there's any room for discussion.
If you're going to do things this way,
then we have nothing to talk about.
Please go back.
Please leave.
Miss Hong, we came here
today with sincerity,
to see how we can cooperate
with you in the future.
Sir,
if you had been sincere,
you wouldn't have used
this kind of ambush tactic today.
Please come back next time.
The door is over there.
-Please move over there.
-Miss Hong, let's talk again.
Or you can state your conditions.
What are you doing?
Don't be so fierce, okay?
Calm down.
Don't push her.
Who are you?
Why are you being so fierce to him?
What happened?
-The Chief of Village brought...
-Chief of Village, we...
Him here without prior notice,
saying they want to talk about
some acquisition agreement.
No, I'm such a good old friend
of your grandpa and dad.
What's there to be uncomfortable about?
Besides, I'm kindly helping
you coordinate.
Look for yourself.
All the residents
have agreed to the acquisition.
-It won't do for only you to stay stuck.
-Chief of Village,
we've all heard
that you privately
went to the 2 neighbors
who didn't want to sell their houses
and told them
that if they persuaded us
to sell our house,
Longxing Group would privately
give them a commission.
That's why they agreed to sell.
How much money did you take from them
to help outsiders force us like this?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean I took money from them?
Didn't you?
You'd better make yourself clear!
I'm telling the truth!
I've been the Chief of Village
for over 10 years,
fair and square!
Don't smear me!
I'm telling you!
What are you talking about?
That's a personal attack!
Calm down, guys.
You're really miserable this time.
You seem to easily get involved
in other people's disputes.
Thank you, Chief.
Actually, for this whole thing,
Zhiling has already gone to
the government agencies, Longxing Group,
and the resident representatives
to get things clear.
The whole plan started 3 years ago,
and the acquisition
didn't start until last year.
Actually, most residents
are very willing to cooperate.
Just...
Everyone should talk nicely.
Except for that Miss Hong.
No amount of communication works.
Calm down.
I know.
You sympathize with Miss Hong
very much, right?
You hope she can keep this old house.
But you have to consider others,
who hope to get their houses rebuilt
and live in a good house quickly.
Everyone has their own stance.
No one is right or wrong.
So I advise you,
don't interfere.
Listen to me.
I heard about Keke at the station.
I told you not to interfere
in other people's business.
Why won't you just listen?
Or is it that
you didn't actually want
to take things as they were,
and you just wanted to be a hero,
acting as if you could save them?
I didn't want to play the hero.
Like I said before,
when I see other people's problems,
I can't just ignore them.
Nothing will happen if you don't help.
Or is it that
if you don't do this...
you won't feel your own worth?
You had group activities in class
when you were a kid, right?
Do you know the feeling
when you turn around,
seeing everyone has a group,
but you're the only one left out?
Once or twice is fine.
But this has been my life
since I was little.
Everyone has their own partners.
It's just me,
not knowing when someone
will come and catch me.
It's like the whole world
has nothing to do with me.
That's why I want
to work hard to prove
that I still deserve
to live in this world.
Ms. Peggy.
Why did you study psychology
instead of music?
I just happened to be assigned to it.
Just because of that?
Yeah, if I like the major, stick with it.
If I don't, just switch.
What about you?
It's because
I want to know others better
and know myself better.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Wait,
you can go to any bar
or nightclub to work.
There are plenty of heartbroken,
unemployed, or crazy people
there for you to study,
and you can also make money.
What about knowing myself better?
Isn't human interaction like a mirror?
When you see other people's problems,
can't you reflect on yourself?
Do you see now
that because of you,
I have been distracted?
Sorry.
Hello?
You prepared so much.
I invited you here specifically
to treat you well, of course.
Sorry for the trouble.
No worries.
Then
I'll dig in.
Eat as much as you want.
And I should be the one thanking you.
This afternoon,
I got a call
from an Academia Sinica research fellow.
He said he was willing to help us
renegotiate with Longxing Group.
My sister and I were so happy
to hear that.
What research fellow? What negotiation?
I thought you knew.
I don't.
The research fellow
has been studying the renovation
and preservation of old houses for years.
And he said a police officer
named Wu Dawei contacted him
and told him all about the renovation
of old houses in our area.
Dawei?
After listening to
the police officer's explanation,
the research fellow
spent some time studying
the overall plan for our area.
He said there should
be a better compromise.
He will help us find a councilor
to renegotiate with the city government
and Longxing Group.
And the research fellow said
it was because the police officer
was very enthusiastic and sincere
that he decided to do this.
So that's what happened.
So,
I think we can get so much help now
all because of you.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
After all, I wasn't the one
who helped in the end.
Besides,
saying this makes me feel so stupid.
I didn't even think
that seeking help
is the most effective way.
You're not stupid.
And,
do you know you actually
have a big influence on me?
What influence?
Well,
I went to protest at Longxing Group
at that time
for a reason.
Didn't you want to keep this old house?
At that time,
I just wanted to let
more people know about this,
so we could have a chance
to negotiate a good price.
But that was because running
this bookstore was really hard.
After going through this whole thing,
I've become more certain
that I really want to keep this old house.
So what they said was true.
I'm sorry.
I'm only telling you now.
We're still friends, right?
Since you're willing to be honest with me,
it's fine.
Then...
cheers.
Cheers.
Cheers means drinking it all.
Why did you only take a sip?
Drink it all?
That's a lot.
Yeah.
Hurry up. Let's race
to see who drinks faster.
We have to race?
The loser gets punished.
-Punished?
-I'm starting.
Dawei.
Are you okay?
Let me tell you,
so many great things happened today,
so I went out to celebrate.
Your face is so red.
How much did you drink?
What are you doing at the bathroom door?
There's a huge cockroach inside.
You wimp.
Don't laugh at me.
I really need to use the bathroom now.
What should I do?
Later, we can count down 5 seconds,
and when we count to one,
you open the door,
and I'll rush in and fight that cockroach
one-on-one.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Ready.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three.
-Two.
One.
This is Two-Minute Love Live Stream.
[Two-Minute Love Live Stream]
It's fleeting, so don't miss it.
[Peggy Talks Love Psychology]
I'm Ms. Peggy.
What I'm going to talk about today
is a bit more difficult.
What I want to talk about today
is a psychological defense mechanism
called
Reaction Formation.
This psychological defense mechanism
is a kind of
unconscious one.
It is usually used to maintain
our confidence or self-esteem.
[Confidence]
[Confidence] [Self-esteem]
And this reaction formation
usually works like this:
In order to hide our true feelings,
we will deliberately act out
the exact opposite emotions or behaviors.
For example,
you really want something,
but you never mention it.
Or,
you really hate a certain colleague,
but when you talk to them,
you are especially polite
and courteous.
In romantic relationships,
it also often happens.
For example,
you obviously like this person very much,
but you pretend not to care.
Okay, in order to
protect our self-esteem,
we may not be able to honestly
and truly display our emotions,
so we use opposite actions
to protect ourselves.
Let me check the comments.
Some girls say no,
but they mean yes.
Is this true?
[Social Rebel Diva]
Hello there.
[Danger]
Do you know that
what you're saying is dangerous?
Okay, I can't continue
the live stream right now.
I need to private message this student.
Okay, bye-bye, everyone.
Goodbye.
Okay.
I have more important things to do now.
Bye-bye.